<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DasomTutorial</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="tv_call_sos">"\"살려줘\" 또는 \"도와줘\" 라고 말해보세요."</string>
    <string name="tv_error_network">"네트워크 연결을 확인해주세요."</string>
    <string name="default_message">Default</string>
    <string name="information_message">information</string>
    <string name="warning_message">warning</string>
    <string name="error_message">error</string>
    <string name="success_message">Success</string>

    <string name="title_introduce">introduce</string>
    <string name="title_dasomtalk">dasomtalk</string>
    <string name="title_videocall">videocall</string>
    <string name="title_sos">sos</string>
    <string name="title_radio">라디오</string>
    <string name="title_medication">medication</string>
    <string name="title_end">end</string>

    <string name="text_sleep_time_question_1">They say that sleep is the best medication for stress. What time did you go to bed last night?</string>
    <string name="text_sleep_time_question_2">I\'m curious, what time did you go to sleep last night?</string>

    <string name="text_wakeup_time_question_1">What time did you wake up this morning?</string>
    <string name="text_wakeup_time_question_2">Do you sleep well these days? What time did you wake up this morning?</string>
    <string name="text_wakeup_time_question_3">Please let me know what time you got up this morning.</string>

    <string name="text_breakfast_question_1">Breakfast is said to be very important in preventing diseases. What delicious food did you have for breakfast?</string>
    <string name="text_breakfast_question_2">They say that breakfast is the most important meal of the day. What did you have for breakfast?</string>
    <string name="text_breakfast_time_question_1">When did you eat breakfast?</string>
    <string name="text_breakfast_time_question_2">What time did you eat breakfast?</string>

    <string name="text_lunch_question_1">Heavy lunches can cause stomach pain. What did you eat for lunch?</string>
    <string name="text_lunch_question_2">Having 3 meals a day is important. What did you have for lunch?</string>
    <string name="text_lunch_time_question_1">What time did you eat lunch?</string>
    <string name="text_lunch_time_question_2">When did you eat lunch?</string>

    <string name="text_dinner_question_1">Having a late dinner can interrupt sleep. What did you eat for dinner?</string>
    <string name="text_dinner_question_2">They say a vegetable-based dinner is good for you. Did you have a vegetable-based dinner? Please tell me what you ate for dinner.</string>
    <string name="text_dinner_question_3">They say that having a light dinner is best. Please let me know what you had for dinner.</string>

    <string name="text_dinner_time_question_1">What time did you eat dinner?</string>

    <string name="text_start_tutorial_1">
        "Hello, I'm a Dasom robot.
        Dasomi can do various things based on artificial intelligence.
        It's not just a normal robot or an ai speaker.\n I can be a caregiver who is alone."
    </string>

    <string name="text_start_tutorial_1_1">
        "Hello, I'm a Dasom robot."
    </string>

    <string name="text_start_tutorial_1_2">
        "Dasomi can do various things based on artificial intelligence."
    </string>

    <string name="text_start_tutorial_1_3">
        "It's not just a normal robot or an ai speaker. I can be a caregiver who is alone."
    </string>

    <string name="text_start_tutorial_2">"I will introduce five things that Dasom Robot can do."</string>

    <string name="text_start_tutorial_3">
        "First, DasomTalk. It’s a community where you can find and chat with friends.
        Second, video calls and messengers. It is a function that allows you to talk with your family.
        Third, emergency notification. When you becomes ill, we notify your family.
        Fourth, the medication reminder. Dasomi will take care of the time to take the medicine.
        Fifth, play a song, play a radio. I'll be a TV and a radio."</string>

    <string name="text_start_tutorial_3_1">
        "First, dasomTalk. It’s a community where you can find and chat with friends."
    </string>

    <string name="text_start_tutorial_3_2">
        "Second, video calls and messengers. It is a function that allows you to talk with your family."
    </string>

    <string name="text_start_tutorial_3_3">
        "Third, emergency notification. When you becomes ill, we notify your family."
    </string>
    <string name="text_start_tutorial_3_4">
        "Fourth, the medication reminder. Dasomi will take care of the time to take the medicine."
    </string>
    <string name="text_start_tutorial_3_5">
        "Fifth, play a song, play a radio. I'll be a TV and a radio."
    </string>

    <string name="text_start_tutorial_4">
        "Now, I will show you one by one in detail. Please watch robot screen carefully, and if the sound is too low, tap the right cheek."</string>
    <string name="text_start_tutorial_4_1">
        "Now, I will show you one by one in detail."
    </string>
    <string name="text_start_tutorial_4_2">
        "Please watch robot screen carefully, and if the sound is too low, tap the right cheek."
    </string>

    <string name="text_start_dasomtalk_tutorial_1">
        "First, I will show you Dasom Talk. Wouldn't it be great if you had a friend to talk to when you're bored or hostile? Meet new friends through me."</string>
    <string name="text_start_dasomtalk_tutorial_1_1">
        "First, I will show you Dasom Talk."</string>
    <string name="text_start_dasomtalk_tutorial_1_2">
        "Wouldn't it be great if you had a friend to talk to when you're bored or hostile? Meet new friends through me."</string>

    <string name="text_start_dasomtalk_tutorial_2">
        "If you are using Dasomi, you can connect from anywhere in the country. How about asking what the weather is like these days and who is your favorite singer?"</string>
    <string name="text_start_dasomtalk_tutorial_2_1">
        "If you are using Dasomi, you can connect from anywhere in the country."
    </string>
    <string name="text_start_dasomtalk_tutorial_2_2">
        "How about asking what the weather is like these days and who is your favorite singer?"
    </string>

    <string name="text_start_videocall_tutorial_1">
       "Second, I will tell you about video calls and messengers. Even if you don't have a smartphone, you can talk to your family through me."
    </string>
    <string name="text_start_videocall_tutorial_1_1">
       "Second, I will tell you about video calls and messengers."
    </string>
    <string name="text_start_videocall_tutorial_1_2">
       "Even if you don't have a smartphone, you can talk to your family through me."
    </string>
    <string name="text_start_videocall_tutorial_2">
        "Please talk often with your family members through me. Dasomi also informed me of the message sent by the guardian."
    </string>
    <string name="text_start_sos_tutorial_1">
        "Next, I will show you the third, emergency alert. You can use emergency alerts when you suddenly get sick or something big happens at home."
    </string>
    <string name="text_start_sos_tutorial_1_1">
        "Next, I will show you the third, emergency alert. "
    </string>
    <string name="text_start_sos_tutorial_1_2">
        "You can use emergency alerts when you suddenly get sick or something big happens at home."
    </string>

    <string name="text_start_sos_tutorial_2">
       "In case of an emergency, don't forget to call \"Dasom-ah\"."
     </string>
    <string name="text_start_medication_tutorial_1">
         "Fourth, I will guide you through the medication reminder. The medication alarm can be set by the guardian or added by the elderly person."
     </string>
    <string name="text_start_medication_tutorial_1_1">
         "Fourth, I will guide you through the medication reminder."
     </string>
    <string name="text_start_medication_tutorial_1_2">
         "The medication alarm can be set by the guardian or added by the elderly person."
     </string>
    <string name="text_start_medication_tutorial_2">
         "It is said that it is good for health if you take your medicine on time. I will tell you, so don't forget to take your medicine."
     </string>
    <string name="text_start_radio_tutorial_1">
         "Finally, I'll tell you about song playback and radio playback."
     </string>
    <string name="text_start_radio_tutorial_2">
         "If you're with Dasomi, you won't be bored."
     </string>
    <string name="text_end_tutorial">
         "How do you like the Dasom robot with so many different functions?
         I may not understand the old man's words well at first, or I may give a wrong answer, but
         If you keep talking to me, Dasomi will become smarter and more intelligent and will be able to give you an appropriate answer.
         If you use it in the future and come across something you are not familiar with, please say \"Introduce yourself\". thank you."
     </string>

    <string name="text_end_tutorial_1_1">
         "How do you like the Dasom robot with so many different functions?"
     </string>
    <string name="text_end_tutorial_1_2_1">
         "At first, I may not understand what you are saying, or I may give you the wrong answer."
     </string>

    <string name="text_end_tutorial_1_2_2">
         "However, if you keep talking to him, Dasomi will become smarter and more intelligent and will be able to give you an appropriate answer."
     </string>

    <string name="text_end_tutorial_1_3">
         " If you use it in the future and come across something you are not familiar with, please say \"Introduce yourself\". "
     </string>

    <string name="text_end_tutorial_1_4">
         " thank you."
     </string>
</resources>